

## CONTACT

ipariola@yahoo.com

**(**234) 810 994 8063

https://pariola.dev

Ilorin. Kwara-state.251101, Nigeria, Africa

# **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF TECH: METALLURGY TECHNOLOGY.

Oct 2018 - Feb 2023

Federal University of Technology, Minna.

## **OTHERS**

Design Systems
PWAs
Software Testing
SE Optimization
Build Automation
Responsive Web Design

# KEHINDE OMOPARIOLA

Creative Front-end engineer

# **ABOUT**

Meet Kehinde Omopariola, a highly productive Frontend Engineer with over two years of experience in building pixel-perfect user interfaces. He is a fast and flexible learner who designs with an eye for detail and a commitment to creating fluid user experiences.

Omopariola has a wealth of experience developing JavaScript applications and strives for performance and scalability. He is a valuable asset to any team and delivers top-quality results.

#### FRONTEND TECHNOLOGIES

Reactjs CSS Preprocessing

Nextjs Gsap
JavaScript (ES6 Hands-on) Mocha
Git Googling

Git Googling
HTML5 & CSS3 Framer-motion

Figma Vuejs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONTEND ENGINEER (FREELANCE)

Regnify Softwares | Oct 2020 - Present.

- At Regnify INC, I worked as a frontend engineer Converting user interfaces from Figma.
- Rebuilt and Redesigned most pages owned by the company.
- Created an inventory management web application and performed the role of a sole front-end engineer utilizing using HTML, SCSS, and React.
- Created an event management web application and performed the role of a sole front-engineer utilizing using Reactjs.

## FRONTEND ENGINEER

Klas INC | May 2021 - Present

- At Klas INC, I worked as a frontend engineer Converting user interfaces from Figma.
- Rebuilt major pages with bleeding-edge technologies.
- Built dynamic mail templates connected SendGrid.

## FRONTEND ENGINEER (FREELANCE)

Diool | April 2022 - Present

- Diool A fintech company focusing on B2B solutions.
- I'm currently working on revamping the whole website designs and page structure.
- I also converted the existing website into Next.js for smooth SE Optimization on our site